Contact

lbookout1@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/laurabookout-bsn-rn-5a95b8a0 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Customer Service Receptionist Duties Learning Quickly

Certifications

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Neonatal Resuscitation Program

Laura Bookout, BSN RN

NICU Registered Nurse at CHOC Children's Irvine

Summary

Current NICU Registered Nurse at CHOC Childrens and BSN Graduate, with Summa Cum Laude honors from West Coast University, with over 3 years of experience in direct patient care. Member of Sigma Theta Tau Honors Society of Nursing and participant in International Studies of Nursing with Global Health scholars in Punta Gorda, Belize. Friendly and enthusiastic employee that is able to learn new tasks quickly and represents organizations with friendly, professional demeanor at all times. Responsible and proficient in excellent communication and time management skills. Handles tasks with accuracy and efficiency.

Student Clinical Rotation Experience
-Preceptorship- Mission Hospital
Units-Oncology/Medical
04/01/18 – 05/20/18 Completed: 90 hours

-Critical Care/Medical Surgical III- La Palma Inter-Community Units- ER, ICU, Telemetry and Medical 01/23/18 – 03/31/18 Completed: 135 hours

-Public Health- SAUSD- McFadden Int. 10/31/17 – 01/22/18 Completed: 90 hours

-Global Public Health: Belize

11/24/17 - 12/09/17 Completed: 60 hours

-Pediatrics- CHOC Children's Hospital Units- NICU, PICU, ER, Medical 08/21/17 – 10/30/17 Completed: 67.5 hours

-Obstetrics- Orange Coast Memorial-UnitsL&D, Post-Partum 06/12/17 – 08/20/17 Completed: 67.5 hours -Medical-Surgical II- Mission Hospital Units- PCSU, CARTEL, ORTHO, ONC 04/02/17 – 06/11/17 Completed: 135 hours

- -Mental Health- La Casa Rehabilitation Center Mental Health 01/22/17 04/01/17 Completed: 90 hours
- -Medical-Surgical I- St. Francis Medical Center Units- Surgical, Medical 10/30/16 – 01/21/17 Completed: 135 hours
- -Fundamentals- Villa Elena Skilled Nursing 08/20/16 10/29/16 Completed: 90 hours

Experience

CHOC Children's Registered Nurse July 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months)

Clinical Nurse in CHOC Children's Level 4 NICU and Small Baby Unit.

Participated in CHOC's RN Residency which allowed me to also obtain my NRP and STABLE certifications.

St Joseph Hospital
Operating Room Assistant
September 2017 - September 2018 (1 year 1 month)
Orange, California

- Ensuring the availability of well-functioning equipment for every surgical case
- Assisting nursing personnel in room set up & turnover and patient support services such as turning, lifting, and transporting patients
- Maintaining a safe and clean work environment in the O.R. suites and peripheral areas.
- Assisting nurses and staff in Pre-Op and PACU with patient care needs, transportation and any assistance requests

Mission Hospital Imaging Partner July 2016 - August 2017 (1 year 2 months)

- Primary objective is assisting Radiologist, nurses and technicians within the radiology department centered around providing patient care to in-patients, traumas, out-patients and ER patients.
- Assist the technologist in preparing the imaging room for a variety of procedures, screening of patients for any contraindications to exams, pulls appropriate equipment and supplies.

Performs a wide variety of duties to include but not limited to: Transporting patients, prepping sterile procedure trays, room turn-over

California Elite Sports Center
Coach / Instructor
November 2010 - August 2016 (5 years 10 months)
Rancho Santa Margarita, CA

- Provide training direction, encouragement, motivation, and advice to prepare athletes for competitive events, practice and for maximum performance.
- Plan and organize events for athletes, maintain safe environment and use leadership skills with my athletes and co-workers.

Michael Andrew Arata MD PC
Patient Care Coordinator
August 2014 - May 2015 (10 months)
Newport Beach, CA

- Schedule and confirm patient appointments, surgeries, or medical consultations for an Interventional Radiologist. Surgeries included Trans-Vascular Autonomic Stimulation, Stem Cell Therapy, and other vascular procedures.
- Completed front and back office responsibilities. Answering phone calls, rooming patients, assisting the nurse and Physician, in-office testing, live scribing, vitals and stocking

Education

West Coast University
Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2015 - 2018)

Tesoro High School
· (2006 - 2010)